So we just checked in at our
hotel here at the Grand Hyatt Jeju
and the room is
spectacular in my opinion.
Paid a little bit extra for the
ocean view and I think it's worth it.
And you can even see
like some incoming planes
landing at the Jeju airport
which is pretty cool.
So after landing in Jeju, we picked up
our rental car which was an EV
decided to go with the IONIQ 5
and yeah, it's really just a pleasure to drive.
I was a little bit concerned about
EV and charging
but if you're staying in the Grand Hyatt,
there's free parking, of course,
if you're staying as a hotel guest
but there's also loads of EV charging spots
that you can use
which makes it super convenient
if you decide to go with an EV.
Other than that, it's been
a pleasure to drive around Jeju.
It's obviously a lot
less chaotic than Seoul or Busan.
If you're like used to
driving in like big cities
Like this should be easy for you
I would say.
You know nothing compared to
Seoul whatsoever.
Alright so we are just outside of Saebil
Saebil, which is like a cafe here in Jeju
and right outside the cafe
there's this pink muhly
It's called Mule or Muhly Grass
and we're taking some photos,
taking some footage
Looks really beautiful,
it's really hot still though
It might not seem that way but
it's pretty warm, it's pretty humid so
But yeah, you gotta do
what you gotta do for some content
First time having Hallabong tangerine,
I believe it's tangerine,
tangerine juice
Ooh, okay it's
different, it's a lot more zingy
It's a lot less orangey.
I expected it to be more like
orange juice,
it's a lot more lighter
What's up babe?
What are you looking at?
Are you looking for snakes?
We just climbed Seongsan Ilchulbong
which is the sunrise peak.
This is obviously not sunrise.
Couldn't be bothered to
wake up that early to do the hike,
but I kinda regret it now
because it's super hot and humid up here.
But other than that, it's
not that difficult to get up here.
I don't think it's that tough,
especially if you're used
to hiking or anything like that.
It's really not that bad.
It's just a lot of steps.
So if you're a Stairmaster, master,
you can probably make it.
And the views up here, I
mean, pretty decent, pretty great.
I think it's probably
better during the sunrise hour.
But still it's worth coming up here
and getting some nice photos.
You can see the
large, green sort of crater.
No lake though, like for example,
Hallasan, there's a lake on top.
But I don't think it's necessary
because you're a crater
and then you'll have a lake.
But still, there's no lake up here.
It's very green.
Just a green volcanic crater.
It's been a great little hike.
And just enjoying the view here with Lisa
for a bit
before we descend down.
Another day, another cafe.
Yeah, just your regular lobster
Not, not anything special
But, you know, I'm all there for the show
The show was awesome,
the guys showed a lot of showmanship
So, five out of ten
for the lobster
And ten out of ten for the showmanship,
definitely.
Do I need some therapy?
Happy, happy, happy...
Is it good? Is it really good?
After a long day of driving,
in this humid,
warm weather we got in Jeju,
nothing beats fresh juice
from this tangerine.
More!
More, more, more!
Hey, what's up everyone. This is Allan
and that's the end of my
Korea vlog series,
if you can call it that.
I was really happy
to be able to visit Jeju
And I just love these
more road trip kind of trips
Just having more freedom to explore
and go where you want, when you want
is just my cup of tea.
But yeah, I can't wait to share more
about my Korea trip
But up next is going to be
a travel guide to Korea
Just packing everything that I've learned
and experienced while traveling here
In a sort of neat package
for anyone who's planning
to visit Korea themselves
So that's currently on
the editing table as we speak.
But overall, Korea was great
and it will certainly not be my last trip.
And finally, I just want to say
thank you for sticking
around to the end of this video
This is Allan.
I'll see you guys in the next one.